# Blake Rochelle

**UXC UX Designer** 

#### Contact

**Address** 

Panama City, FL, 32401

**Phone** 

(256) 404-1521

E-mail

blakerochelle@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/blakerochelle/

www

https://blakerochelle.github.io/

## **Skills**

Iterative Development

Excellent

**UX** Design

Very Good

**UI Prototyping** 

Very Good

Responsive Design

Excellent

HTML SCSS Javascript
JQuery

Excellent

Highly skilled UX designer and front-end web developer with 15 years experience in designing and integrating new website functionality and prototyping interactive product application interfaces. Designed a consumer web rater that increased annual direct sales by \$650,000 per year and a user research tool that cut research time in half, significantly reduced risk and improved annual revenue loss by ~\$250,000.

## **Work History**

2010-09 -Current

### **UX** Designer

Kemper Corporation, Previously Infinity Insurance, Birmingham, AL

- Lead UX designer for Infinity Insurance
- Promoted and ensured consistent look, feel and experience across multiple Kemper/Infinity domains and platforms.
- Defined user experience concepts and provided design layouts, workflows, prototypes and high-fidelity graphics.
- Created and maintained libraries of reusable web components.
- Closely collaborated with cross-functional teams and business units to turn requirements into completed apps, within project deadlines, and to identify and quickly address problems.
- Developed and facilitated UX workshops, to help promote optimum user experience across the organization, with 95% positive feedback from attendees.

2003-10 -2010-09

## Lead Web Developer

Red Mountain Technologies, Birmingham, AL

- Utilized user-centric principals to design and develop web-based applications.
- Maintained existing applications to ensure their accuracy and currency.
- Performed technical support duties and customer interaction training.
- Served as project coordinator which included managing current project goals as well as long term team goals.

 Planned, designed and prepared company newsletter for digital and print dissemination.

#### 2002-02 -2003-10

## **Customer Service Representative**

AutoCheck Auctions, Birmingham, AL

- Vehicle history data provider to over 95% of the auction industry.
- Interacted one-on-one with customers to help serve their individual needs.
- Coordinated with management to strengthen relationships with our customers.
- Analyzed various data streams to determine the accuracy of historical vehicle information.

#### **Education**

1997-09 -2001-12 Bachelor of Science: Business Administration, Management Information Systems

Auburn University - Auburn, AL

# **Certifications**

2018-03

UX Certification, Nielsen Norman Group